<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>SARD JV Limited</title>
    <description>Appraisal and revalidation management software for doctors and nurses. A joint venture between Oxleas NHS Foundation Trust and Mango Swiss Limited.</description>
    <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>SARD launches new partnership with Mind in Croydon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be working with Mind in Croydon to raise funds for people and their families living with mental health issues in our local area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be holding our Stand Up to Stigma event before the end of the year, a night of comedy in aid of this fantastic charity. More details to follow soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On 26 October Kevin, Phil, Sophie and Barbara from the SARD team will be taking part in the Great South Run, with all sponsorship raised also being donated to Mind in Croydon. The team can be sponsored online at www.justgiving.com/runningsard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mind in Croydon is a very active charity that works with people with mental health problems and their families in Croydon. It aims to increase understanding of the difficulties faced by those with mental health problems. Its various projects help to relieve social isolation, enable people to acquire skills for independent life and promote positive mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information can be be found on their website www.mindincroydon.org.uk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Registered Charity number 1073880.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/06/05/mind-in-croydon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/06/05/mind-in-croydon.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/news/19bde1be.mind_in_croydon.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Development - SARD announces development of Appraisal for all system</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;SARD are pleased to announce that it is further developing the capability of its platform to extend the system in order to cover the appraisal process for all staff. It is a logical step as we already know our revalidation and appraisal system helps thousands of doctors and we felt that our system could further support other colleagues within the NHS. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project plans have been drawn up and development is about to start. We are very excited about what we can produce and more importantly how this can help organisations to run, record and report on appraisals for all staff.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/06/05/appraisal-for-all.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/06/05/appraisal-for-all.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/news/0947e14d.scrum_timer.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sussex Communities joins SARD</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that Sussex Community NHS Foundation Trust has just recently signed up to use the SARD Revalidation and Appraisal system. Implementation is underway and we are looking forward to this new partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/05/28/sussex-communities-joins-sard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/news/2014/05/28/sussex-communities-joins-sard.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/news/07633dad.sussex_community_website.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>This Week</title>
        <description>This week has been a very exciting week for us and for me. We have been building a new website to reflect all of the new exciting things we are doing. I have enjoyed really getting my teeth stuck into helping to build and design something that shows our current clients and potential clients what we are capable of, but more importantly why we do it. I often feel that businesses focus on a product, what they are building, but I don&#39;t think clients just look for what you can do, they want to see that you are doing it for the right reasons. For me it is about values, if we can bring our values to work and translate them in to building great things that we care about and believe in then by extension what we produce will be the best can be. I know people may question the idea of how you can care about building a system, and really what impact does it have, but to be honest the system is really the vehicle, it is believing in what you do and not just doing it because it is there. I have a firm held belief in trying to improve things, make them better and easier and that is reflected both inside and outside of work. I hope that the work we are doing with this internal website project reflects this.</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/philip/2014/06/11/this-week.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/philip/2014/06/11/this-week.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/philip/405898cf.website_screen_shot.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer service in our sleep</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I had some time off this month for an operation and was fortunate enough to be treated in the day surgery unit of Princess Royal University Hospital, now run by Kings College Hospital NHS FT. When my anaesthetist and her assistant asked me what I did, I don’t think they were expecting to be asked if they liked their appraisal software!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, the anaesthetist had used SARD to complete her appraisal in April and said she liked the system very much. Unfortunately, I was out for the count before I could ask her for a full testimonial!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to get an MSF form to see it from the patient side. Maybe next time.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/francesca/2014/06/07/customer-service-in-our-sleep.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/francesca/2014/06/07/customer-service-in-our-sleep.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/francesca/e74bcff2.kings-standard-general.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silicon Triangle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2013 Kevin and I discussed the fact that we often ran into small technical problems and we realised that there must be a wealth of technical resource in our area. Crystal Palace is historically linked to the principles of advancing through science and technology and bringing all new innovation together in one place. Kevin, as you may expect, has a keen interest in all types of technology, and I have a passion for most things science (even the bad bits are usually fascinating). From this grew the idea of the Silicon Triangle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We put a poster up in our local pub, the Grape and Grain, on which we invited those with an interest in science and technology to join us in rekindling the spirit of the original Crystal Palace.  And on August 6th we got together. It was a modest group of people that responded, but it was a lot of fun. We all sat around, had a drink and chatted about our respective science &amp;amp; tech backgrounds. Kevin found people who inspired him to design different features for SARD and I found people who were happy to have me talk epigenetics at them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past 11 months the Silicon Triangle grew and interesting things kept coming up. People brought their new gadgets to the pub to show them off and in April one of the attendees even brought their own 3D printer with some printed models to show off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were really impressed with how many people the gathering attracted and how many return members we had. By now we started to realise that the Grape and Grain pub, though having been extremely hospitable, was no longer a suitable venue. We needed a place of our own! So after taking May off to rethink the way we were organising the Silicon Triangle. I went to a meeting at West Norwood’s The Open Works initiative (link: http://www.theopenworks.org/) to talk about a local maker space to see if perhaps the Silicon Triangle could relocate to this location, or if this would be a viable change. Unfortunately the Open Works’ maker space is still in such an early stage that this was not viable. I spoke to the people of the South London Maker Space (link: http://www.southlondonmakerspace.org/) to see what they had to offer, but at that point they were about to lose their space in Herne Hill (luckily by now they’ve found a more permanent location). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other question was whether we wanted a space where we could work on a project together, or we wanted a place where we could all socialise and perhaps listen to others talk about projects. With the 2 maker space options not entirely up to scratch, I decided that a room above a pub or similar venue would be perfectly fine for our purposes for now. And so I got in touch with the lovely people from the Antenna café (link: http://www.antennastudios.co.uk/cafe-thing/) who were up for hosting our night. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We eventually returned on the 3rd of June with a new venue and a beautiful new poster design by Steve Horry that you can see as the title picture of this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/sophie/2014/06/06/silicon-triangle.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/sophie/2014/06/06/silicon-triangle.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/sophie/145394ea.silicon-triangle.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>i-Luddite</title>
        <description>If you just keep asking questions you eventually start knowing things, which is initially disconcerting but ultimately feels good, like gradually getting into a too hot bath. Now when I type into a password box and it replaces letters with little circles, I don’t assume it is witchcraft. I am slowly becoming one of them.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/nicholas/2014/06/03/i-luddite.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/nicholas/2014/06/03/i-luddite.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/nicholas/e5bfcd47.i-luddite.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to work</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is my first day back in the office after a week in Portugal with my family. Getting back into the swing of things can be a challenge but today I was really keen to get back and getting cracking on setting up our charity events in aid of Mind in Croydon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several local businesses in the Crystal Palace area have already pledged their support and I am now working on pulling all the events together, including our Goldmine Treasure Hunt, Stand up to Stigma comedy event and the Great South Run, they should all be really fun events which we are all very much looking forward to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news it was great to come back and find out how the Nursing Appraisal Conference that Phil and Sophie exhibited at went. Its good to know that everyone there responded positively to our intention to launch Appraisal for All (name to be confirmed). It is good to know that we are continuing to meet genuine client need.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/francesca/2014/05/23/back-to-work.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/francesca/2014/05/23/back-to-work.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/francesca/06a23ee0.portugal.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nurse Appraisal Conference</title>
        <description>We recently attended the &#39;Nursing Appraisal and Revalidation&#39; conference in London, which was a very useful and insightful event. Having a background plunged into the inner depths of medical revalidation and as a company looking to expand our systems to fulfill future requirements, this conference could not have come at a better time. I think there was a little nervousness about readiness, both from our persepctive and from those who will have to undertake this process. However this conference managed to highlight some important anxiety busters. Firstly, although things are moving quickly, no final decisions have been made, which is useful for us as we want to make sure we are part of the process and develop solutions that meet the actual need and not the percieved one. Secondly, it was clear that it was a well thought out process and the NMC were trying to ensure that Nurse revalidation met the requirements of nurses and was not just a carbon copy of revalidation for doctors.</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/philip/2014/05/22/nurse-appraisal-conference.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sardjv.co.uk/blog/philip/2014/05/22/nurse-appraisal-conference.html</guid>
        <media:content url="http://www.sardjv.co.uk/images/blog/philip/8e13e131.nurse_appraisal_conference.jpg" medium="image" width="120" height="120"/>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
